<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Relay on BRYSGO</title>
    <link>http://brysgo.com/tags/relay/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Relay on BRYSGO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 01:13:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brysgo.com/tags/relay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Imaginary Lines</title>
      <link>http://brysgo.com/2016/04/01/imaginary-lines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brysgo.com/2016/04/01/imaginary-lines/</guid>
      <description>If I had to sum up the job of a software engineer in laymen&amp;rsquo;s terms, I would tell you that we draw imaginary lines around imaginary concepts until those concepts can map to both a specific set of instructions for a machine and a common understanding for programmers.
Why am I stating the obvious? Well, it is quite simply to emphasize just how important it is where we draw those lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GraphiQL Bookmarklet</title>
      <link>http://brysgo.com/2015/12/19/graphiql-bookmarklet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 13:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brysgo.com/2015/12/19/graphiql-bookmarklet/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;m sure most of you, if you have done any work with graphql, have heard of graphiql. It is an indespensible tool for writing and testing graphql queries.
The problem is that now that I&amp;rsquo;m not using express at the moment. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to go through the trouble of trying to fit graphiql into my stack.
To solve it, a graphiql bookmarklet:  Enjoy! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Relay replace Flux?</title>
      <link>http://brysgo.com/2015/07/25/relay-vs-flux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brysgo.com/2015/07/25/relay-vs-flux/</guid>
      <description>Relay is out in preview! Have a look.
 When people talk about Relay they think of it as the server-client link in the Facebook stack, but is that really all it is?
Flux still has a place on the client because you need to manage temporary app state, right?
I think it doesn&amp;rsquo;t. Flux is an architecture for unidirectional data flow that separates out input from the user and the server so that it can react without getting tangled up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Excited for Facebook&#39;s Relay and GraphQL</title>
      <link>http://brysgo.com/2015/07/08/why-relay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brysgo.com/2015/07/08/why-relay/</guid>
      <description>Relay is out in preview! Have a look.
 I want to tell you in as few words as possible why I am so excited to get my hands on Relay and GraphQL.
React is widely popular because it is simple and declarative, making it very deterministic and easy to work with. React is also fully composable, making it imensly powerful with high potential for writing reusable code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>