<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>life on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/life/</link><description>Recent content in life on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:03:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My AI Story (1/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</guid><description>If I&amp;rsquo;m going to start writing about AI, I figure I should give some backstory first on my life in AI.
My first introduction to AI was probably when I was 9 years old and snuck downstairs to watch the first Matrix movie that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to be watching. This did a great deal to feed what has become an AI obsession over the years.
In high school, after I had been programming on my own for a while with only stack overflow to guide me (plus a couple people who volunteered to help me with my shareware), I started pondering about AI from the perspective of how it worked.</description></item><item><title>Kitchen Experiments: the weirdest way to cook</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</guid><description>As COVID-19 settled in and the outside food procurement grew fraught with uncertainty, I turned to something I managed to avoid for a very long time&amp;hellip; cooking.
My solution to this problem was to geek out on my love of science, minimalism, and efficiency to create tasty, weird, nutritious food that doesn&amp;rsquo;t upset my stomach or other parts of my body. You may be wondering about that last one, but I can assure you, when you start playing with discrete chemical ingredients to make your food, having the wrong combination of foods can lead to a unique experience.</description></item></channel></rss>