<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>life on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/life/</link><description>Recent content in life on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 08:05:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>COVID Blues: Picking the Scab</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-09-22-COVID-Blues-Picking-096f66/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 08:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-09-22-COVID-Blues-Picking-096f66/</guid><description>They say that it isn&amp;rsquo;t good to think about profound things when you are feeling down, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to break the rules and attempt to dissect my unhappiness and lay it bare. I&amp;rsquo;m doing this because I know I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one who experiences internal conflict and I think by writing about it I can not only show people that it is normal, but perhaps help someone else reason their way out of it.</description></item><item><title>the yin and yang of utility</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-08-the-yin-and-yang-of-dc939a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 17:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-08-the-yin-and-yang-of-dc939a/</guid><description>I just did some dehydrating exercise in the sun, so this will be what amounts to some pontificating shower thoughts. But you already clicked on the link so you might as well read it.
While trying to solve the knapsack problem I got to thinking about the realities of maximizing utility. Since I am a software engineer and engineering is just building tools to maximize utility, I let my mind frolic down that sweet sweet rabbit hole.</description></item><item><title>Holding in the Idea Vomit</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-29-Holding-in-the-Idea-1541f1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 08:04:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-29-Holding-in-the-Idea-1541f1/</guid><description>Yesterday I had an idea. Congratulations me, now there are two options, I can:
Take the red pill - see how deep the rabbit hole goes Take the blue pill - be blissfully ignorant of whether my new idea will work The free spirit I am, has lots of trouble with #2 because I am insatiably curious and hate myself. But I recognize that I need to learn how to do this, or I will spend my life jumping from rabbit hole to rabbit hole like a prairie dog.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (3/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-26-My-AI-Story-33-11a67c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-26-My-AI-Story-33-11a67c/</guid><description>After graduating with my BS in Computer Science, AI moved to side project status as I took a job as a Full Stack Software Engineer at Pivotal Labs. The side project years of my AI life made slow progress. I managed to play with some algorithms that one time when I was trying to learn golang. I eventually implemented my logic gate pool genetic algorithm as part of a more ambitions side project I called thoughtnet.</description></item><item><title>project review time</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-24-project-review-time-1a1913/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 08:04:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-24-project-review-time-1a1913/</guid><description>I recently got a good review at work and it helped me start to course correct a dangerous internal narrative. For the last year of projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been on, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard: &amp;ldquo;you are a genius, but you have to work on your communication&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; which in my brain translates to &amp;ldquo;we need to soften the blow of this feedback, but you are a piece of shit to work with&amp;rdquo;
Truth is, when you hear something enough times, you start to believe it.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (2/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-21-My-AI-Story-23-e5cf6d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 17:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-21-My-AI-Story-23-e5cf6d/</guid><description>Learning in school was very difficult for me because I was more of a hands on learner and school was very heavy on lecturing. When I am in situations that frustrate me, I try and solve them with technology. This was what I had planned to do with my ed tech company &amp;ldquo;Socrenchus.&amp;rdquo; Before Socrenchus though, I was interning in Mountain View and I got to meet some of the AI great&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>Seitan is a dish best served cold</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 08:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</guid><description>My first kitchen obsession of the quarantine season, was Seitan. The reason being that it is delicious, and I can make it entirely with ingredients shipped via Amazon. While this mostly appeals to me because I didn&amp;rsquo;t much feel like going to the super market, it also helped that I&amp;rsquo;m a huge nerd and I like the idea of creating something out of simple powdered ingredients.
It was a bumpy road to getting it right.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (1/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</guid><description>If I&amp;rsquo;m going to start writing about AI, I figure I should give some backstory first on my life in AI.
My first introduction to AI was probably when I was 9 years old and snuck downstairs to watch the first Matrix movie that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to be watching. This did a great deal to feed what has become an AI obsession over the years.
In high school, after I had been programming on my own for a while with only stack overflow to guide me (plus a couple people who volunteered to help me with my shareware), I started pondering about AI from the perspective of how it worked.</description></item><item><title>Kitchen Experiments: the weirdest way to cook</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</guid><description>As COVID-19 settled in and the outside food procurement grew fraught with uncertainty, I turned to something I managed to avoid for a very long time&amp;hellip; cooking.
My solution to this problem was to geek out on my love of science, minimalism, and efficiency to create tasty, weird, nutritious food that doesn&amp;rsquo;t upset my stomach or other parts of my body. You may be wondering about that last one, but I can assure you, when you start playing with discrete chemical ingredients to make your food, having the wrong combination of foods can lead to a unique experience.</description></item></channel></rss>