<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>opinion on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/opinion/</link><description>Recent content in opinion on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 08:04:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Health Pro's and Con's of Cooking with Discrete Ingredients</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-03-Health-Pros-and-Con-d615f2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 08:04:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-03-Health-Pros-and-Con-d615f2/</guid><description>Remember when I mentioned that cooking with discrete ingredients has side effects? Well, in reality, all food has side effects, they are just drowned out by the popular proportions of everything that are hard coded into the common foods that everyone eats.
When you start experimenting with specific ingredients, you throw that all away. Suddenly, you will find yourself rapidly trying to diagnose something with Google and fix it with another ingredient that you normally eat all the time.</description></item><item><title>A letter to police</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-12-A-letter-to-police-5086c8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 17:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-12-A-letter-to-police-5086c8/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not usually outwardly political, but I have something to get off my chest. I recently overheard a police officer talking about how it won&amp;rsquo;t be worth it if he has to get insurance so he won&amp;rsquo;t get sued. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable enough to get into a debate with him, which later made me even more uncomfortable, so I will address the issue here.
When you signed up to be a public servant and put yourself in harms way to protect your community, it was one of the noblest and bravest things you could do.</description></item><item><title>The Dangers of Idiomatic Programming</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-12-07-idiom-shmidiom/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-12-07-idiom-shmidiom/</guid><description>What does it mean to be idiomatic?
&amp;ldquo;Of, relating to, or conforming to idiom&amp;rdquo; - Merriam-Webster
So what is an idiom?
&amp;ldquo;The syntactical, grammatical, or structural form peculiar to a language&amp;rdquo; - Merriam-Webster
When we talk about idiomatic programming, we are talking about doing things because it is &amp;ldquo;the way&amp;rdquo; to do them, or because so-and-so says this is a rule that can’t be broken.
Why is it important to see past these idioms and understand why they are &amp;ldquo;the way?</description></item><item><title>The Job of an OS</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-06-job-of-os/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-06-job-of-os/</guid><description>It started with a gitter chat then a tweet, followed by a blog post.
&amp;hellip;
Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some time to digest my thoughts, and I think it is time for, a second blog post.
Whenever I think something needs redefining, the first thing I like to do is look for a definition (shocking right?). The Merriam-Webster dictionary defines and Operating System as:
Software that controls the operation of a computer and directs the processing of programs (as by assigning storage space in memory and controlling input and output functions)</description></item><item><title>Why are operating systems still multi-user?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-05-multi-user-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-05-multi-user-systems/</guid><description>So I&amp;rsquo;m minding my own business, setting up Arch linux in my unrooted Termux installation on my phone, when all of a sudden, makepkg wants me to not be root to run a build. Excuse me? What century are we in?
Let me clarify, when I am running linux in a container to build applications the operating system should not be bothering me with arbitrary user systems.
When was the last time you logged into a multi-user unix system that had other users on it?</description></item></channel></rss>