<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>devops on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/devops/</link><description>Recent content in devops on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 08:04:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GitHub Inbox Zero</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-14-GitHub-Inbox-Zero-9892d6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 08:04:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-14-GitHub-Inbox-Zero-9892d6/</guid><description>I recently reached inbox zero on GitHub for the first time in a long time. A while ago I got freaked out by the possibility of people stealing my secret keys through CI and I disabled my CI tokens on my zillion GitHub repos. It was all broken windows from there. Before I knew it my GitHub was a graveyard of packages with out of date dependencies that I had no time to update.</description></item><item><title>New Landing Page - New Commitment</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-11-new-landing-page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-11-new-landing-page/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to redo my landing page in response to a realization that I need to sell myself a bit better. While this post isn&amp;rsquo;t related to the topics tagged above, it is a placeholder for my commitment to put some more effort into publishing here.</description></item><item><title>Why are operating systems still multi-user?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-05-multi-user-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-05-multi-user-systems/</guid><description>So I&amp;rsquo;m minding my own business, setting up Arch linux in my unrooted Termux installation on my phone, when all of a sudden, makepkg wants me to not be root to run a build. Excuse me? What century are we in?
Let me clarify, when I am running linux in a container to build applications the operating system should not be bothering me with arbitrary user systems.
When was the last time you logged into a multi-user unix system that had other users on it?</description></item><item><title>React Native on Heroku</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/07/26/react-native-on-heroku/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/07/26/react-native-on-heroku/</guid><description>As a web developer doing iOS development with react native, I need a staging environment for the product manager to review changes to the app.
On the web, that means using Heroku, but with a react native app it is a bit more complicated.
My react native app has two components, the packager (for serving the client code) and the server (for interacting with the app).
Heroku only lets one process bind to an external port, so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy to do without creating two heroku apps.</description></item><item><title>Teaspoon with Capybara-Webkit</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/02/teaspoon-with-capybara-webkit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/02/teaspoon-with-capybara-webkit/</guid><description>Do you use teaspoon to run your javascript tests? Do you use Capybara-Webkitto run your feature tests? Now you can run your teaspoon suite faster without having to install and boot up phantomjs. Just use the new Capybara-Webkit driver for teaspoon!You may also have more success with it on your CI server, as that is what caused us to make this change.</description></item></channel></rss>