<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shower thoughts on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/shower-thoughts/</link><description>Recent content in shower thoughts on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 08:05:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/shower-thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>$trong AI</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-09-10-dollartrong-AI-f769ed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 08:05:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-09-10-dollartrong-AI-f769ed/</guid><description>When it was announced not too long ago, GPT-3 set a new standard for the size of an AI model at a whopping 175 billion parameters, and an estimated cost of at least $4.6 million. Ever since the first closed beta examples started showing up, it has been blowing people&amp;rsquo;s minds and causing everyone to think about what is next.
One of the best things about programming (and open source in particular) is that everyone can play and have access to everything they need to build cool stuff.</description></item><item><title>the yin and yang of utility</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-08-the-yin-and-yang-of-dc939a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 17:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-08-the-yin-and-yang-of-dc939a/</guid><description>I just did some dehydrating exercise in the sun, so this will be what amounts to some pontificating shower thoughts. But you already clicked on the link so you might as well read it.
While trying to solve the knapsack problem I got to thinking about the realities of maximizing utility. Since I am a software engineer and engineering is just building tools to maximize utility, I let my mind frolic down that sweet sweet rabbit hole.</description></item><item><title>Health Pro's and Con's of Cooking with Discrete Ingredients</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-03-Health-Pros-and-Con-d615f2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 08:04:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-03-Health-Pros-and-Con-d615f2/</guid><description>Remember when I mentioned that cooking with discrete ingredients has side effects? Well, in reality, all food has side effects, they are just drowned out by the popular proportions of everything that are hard coded into the common foods that everyone eats.
When you start experimenting with specific ingredients, you throw that all away. Suddenly, you will find yourself rapidly trying to diagnose something with Google and fix it with another ingredient that you normally eat all the time.</description></item><item><title>Holding in the Idea Vomit</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-29-Holding-in-the-Idea-1541f1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 08:04:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-29-Holding-in-the-Idea-1541f1/</guid><description>Yesterday I had an idea. Congratulations me, now there are two options, I can:
Take the red pill - see how deep the rabbit hole goes Take the blue pill - be blissfully ignorant of whether my new idea will work The free spirit I am, has lots of trouble with #2 because I am insatiably curious and hate myself. But I recognize that I need to learn how to do this, or I will spend my life jumping from rabbit hole to rabbit hole like a prairie dog.</description></item></channel></rss>