<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>humor on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/humor/</link><description>Recent content in humor on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 17:04:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/humor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vegan Insomnia Beef in Ginger Sauce</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-16-Vegan-Insomnia-Beef-cc6199/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 17:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-16-Vegan-Insomnia-Beef-cc6199/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going back and forth for a little while with my sister about trying to recreate a seitan ginger beef dish from a restaurant that we like in Vermont. It is a little tricky for me since I&amp;rsquo;ve never done a seitan beef before and because of the whole low FODMAP thing, but I finally decided to give it a try. After substituting pretty much every ingredient in the recipes I found, I finally created what I lovingly refer to as insomnia beef, since I associate eating it with not being the least bit tired (probably because of the high protein content and the cocoa nibs I threw in).</description></item><item><title>Holding in the Idea Vomit</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-29-Holding-in-the-Idea-1541f1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 08:04:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-29-Holding-in-the-Idea-1541f1/</guid><description>Yesterday I had an idea. Congratulations me, now there are two options, I can:
Take the red pill - see how deep the rabbit hole goes Take the blue pill - be blissfully ignorant of whether my new idea will work The free spirit I am, has lots of trouble with #2 because I am insatiably curious and hate myself. But I recognize that I need to learn how to do this, or I will spend my life jumping from rabbit hole to rabbit hole like a prairie dog.</description></item></channel></rss>