<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>quirky on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/quirky/</link><description>Recent content in quirky on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 08:04:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/quirky/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>project review time</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-24-project-review-time-1a1913/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 08:04:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-24-project-review-time-1a1913/</guid><description>I recently got a good review at work and it helped me start to course correct a dangerous internal narrative. For the last year of projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been on, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard: &amp;ldquo;you are a genius, but you have to work on your communication&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; which in my brain translates to &amp;ldquo;we need to soften the blow of this feedback, but you are a piece of shit to work with&amp;rdquo;
Truth is, when you hear something enough times, you start to believe it.</description></item><item><title>Seitan is a dish best served cold</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 08:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</guid><description>My first kitchen obsession of the quarantine season, was Seitan. The reason being that it is delicious, and I can make it entirely with ingredients shipped via Amazon. While this mostly appeals to me because I didn&amp;rsquo;t much feel like going to the super market, it also helped that I&amp;rsquo;m a huge nerd and I like the idea of creating something out of simple powdered ingredients.
It was a bumpy road to getting it right.</description></item><item><title>Kitchen Experiments: the weirdest way to cook</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</guid><description>As COVID-19 settled in and the outside food procurement grew fraught with uncertainty, I turned to something I managed to avoid for a very long time&amp;hellip; cooking.
My solution to this problem was to geek out on my love of science, minimalism, and efficiency to create tasty, weird, nutritious food that doesn&amp;rsquo;t upset my stomach or other parts of my body. You may be wondering about that last one, but I can assure you, when you start playing with discrete chemical ingredients to make your food, having the wrong combination of foods can lead to a unique experience.</description></item><item><title>New Landing Page - New Commitment</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-11-new-landing-page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-11-new-landing-page/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to redo my landing page in response to a realization that I need to sell myself a bit better. While this post isn&amp;rsquo;t related to the topics tagged above, it is a placeholder for my commitment to put some more effort into publishing here.</description></item><item><title>Quarantine Rule #2: Play Video Games</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-09-video-games/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-09-video-games/</guid><description>While we are physically isolated from each-other, we are missing the ability to go out and make new experiences with the people we care about as well as spontaneous experiences with people we&amp;rsquo;ve never seen before.
We are all connected with each-other via the internet, but the internet lacks the richness of experiences that you get in the real world. While this is true to some degree, if you dive into the world of video games, you will quickly realize that it can provide some pretty incredible experiences that make you forget you are at home in your apartment.</description></item><item><title>Quarantine Rule #1: Exercise every day</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-workout/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-workout/</guid><description>It may sound like a lot, but if you are like me and your quarantine space is limited to a studio apartment, then it is probably the most essential thing you can do to stay sane. The three groups of exercise I alternate between are:
Anaerobic Aerobic Stretching As an experienced introvert, it may not come as a surprise to you that exercise is one of the things I tend to go long periods neglecting, but in this new COVID-19 world, I decided it was mission critical so I went on a YouTube research quest to figure out what I was going to do for exercise.</description></item><item><title>Quarantine Tips from Experienced Introvert</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-life/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-life/</guid><description>The year is 2003. It is a lovely spring day and I can see out my window where the trees and birds sing. Then a yell comes from downstairs, it is my mother telling me it is so nice out I should come outside. The temptation is strong, but the draw of my new computer that I had been obsessing over is even stronger.
Fast-forward to 2020. COVID-19 terrorizes the world and we are all forced to quarantine until god knows when.</description></item><item><title>The Dangers of Idiomatic Programming</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-12-07-idiom-shmidiom/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-12-07-idiom-shmidiom/</guid><description>What does it mean to be idiomatic?
&amp;ldquo;Of, relating to, or conforming to idiom&amp;rdquo; - Merriam-Webster
So what is an idiom?
&amp;ldquo;The syntactical, grammatical, or structural form peculiar to a language&amp;rdquo; - Merriam-Webster
When we talk about idiomatic programming, we are talking about doing things because it is &amp;ldquo;the way&amp;rdquo; to do them, or because so-and-so says this is a rule that can’t be broken.
Why is it important to see past these idioms and understand why they are &amp;ldquo;the way?</description></item><item><title>The Job of an OS</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-06-job-of-os/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-06-job-of-os/</guid><description>It started with a gitter chat then a tweet, followed by a blog post.
&amp;hellip;
Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some time to digest my thoughts, and I think it is time for, a second blog post.
Whenever I think something needs redefining, the first thing I like to do is look for a definition (shocking right?). The Merriam-Webster dictionary defines and Operating System as:
Software that controls the operation of a computer and directs the processing of programs (as by assigning storage space in memory and controlling input and output functions)</description></item><item><title>Back to the blog...</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/11/back-to-the-blog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 01:19:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/11/back-to-the-blog/</guid><description>Now I know this isn&amp;rsquo;t my first time promising more blog time but I&amp;rsquo;m renewing my vows.
I&amp;rsquo;m not going to be so rigid with my every day blog promise, but I will make an effort where possible. Also, I plan on doing something which I haven&amp;rsquo;t done before which is try to keep my blog posts up to date.
If you go back through my blog posts you will see edits and updates to make sure I can stay proud of my blog instead of being unconfident of stale blog posts.</description></item><item><title>The Seesaw First Five Days</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/09/the-seesaw-first-five-days/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 17:57:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/09/the-seesaw-first-five-days/</guid><description>The Seesaw First Five Daysfrancinegoldsteinmarketblog:
January 8, 2015
Happy new year! Volatility is alive and well!
Let’s recap the first five days: the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index sold off 2.7% for the first three days and then surged 3.0% for the next two days.
The sharp stock market volatility has proved especially challenging for all but the nimblest&amp;hellip;
Thanks for the advice, seems like a fairly low risk / low maintenance way to maintain a portfolio.</description></item><item><title>18 Years of Crohn's, 1 Week of Soylent 1.3</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/03/18-years-of-crohns-1-week-of-soylent-1-3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2015 12:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/03/18-years-of-crohns-1-week-of-soylent-1-3/</guid><description>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>
&lt;strong>UPDATE:&lt;/strong> The nutritionist suggested I stop soylent after
version 1.4 made me irregular and wasn't helping me keep on weight. 1.5
looks better but I am going to wait a little before diving back in.
&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Here is a quick synopsis of my case&amp;hellip;&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>
&lt;em
>I was diagnosed with Crohn&amp;rsquo;s disease when I was 7 years old. I have
managed to avoid surgery, but was a frequent flyer in the emergency room
for flare ups. I was on remicade for about ten years and have been on
mercaptopurine and mesalamine since I was diagnosed. I was
on antibiotics from the time I was diagnosed until I graduated college,
and somewhere in that span I was briefly on growth hormones and steroids.
Additionally, I am most recently back on antibiotics and budesonide.&lt;/em
>
&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>
My most recent flare up a few months ago is what put me on budesonide and a
few weeks before I started soylent I went back on antibiotics (tinidazole and
ciprofloxacin). I ordered soylent months ago and was delighted when Soylent
V1.3 arrived in the midst of me trying to control my symptoms.</description></item><item><title>A RoseFactory by any other name...</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/18/a-rosefactory-by-any-other-name/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 22:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/18/a-rosefactory-by-any-other-name/</guid><description>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>
There are only two hard things in Computer Science: cache invalidation and
naming things.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>— Phil Karlton&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>
Lets hold on to cache invalidation for another post&lt;a
href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g-4-gLlF0uw"
>…&lt;/a
>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Naming things (or should I say labeling them&lt;a
href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g-4-gLlF0uw"
>…&lt;/a
>) is a very hard problem.
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>Why is it a hard problem?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>
Consider this, imagine you are building a piece of IKEA furniture. You get all
the pieces in the box and you have to put them together. Now imagine that all
the pieces had a succinct description that you used to put them together. Now
imagine that you couldn’t see or feel the pieces and all you had to work with
were these descriptions.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;img
alt=""
src="http://photos1.blogger.com/blogger2/1715/1669/1600/larson-oct-1987.gif"
/>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p></description></item><item><title>UX that grows complexity with the user, not the product</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/ux-that-grows-complexity-with-the-user-not-the/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/ux-that-grows-complexity-with-the-user-not-the/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
Have you ever played a videogame where you sit down, turn on the game, and are
overwhelmed with a thousand cool things you can do?*
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>NO&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Why not? Because that game company went out of business long ago. Games start
with one thing the user can do, waits until the user is comfortable, then
introduces the next thing.</description></item><item><title>Blogs on blogs on blogs</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/if-i-write-a-blog-in-the-forest-does-it-make-a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 13:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/if-i-write-a-blog-in-the-forest-does-it-make-a/</guid><description>I’ve decided to write a blog post every day, even if it is crappy. Why? Is it so I can feel important? Maybe, but I would never admit that. The reason I’m sticking to is that I want to get better at reflecting on important parts of my day. It may help me appreciate all the interesting things I come across daily that are quickly relegated to a distant memory.</description></item><item><title>Wishlist Series</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/07/27/wishlist-series/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 21:55:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/07/27/wishlist-series/</guid><description>Those of you who know me already know I am a man of many wishes and dreams. That means as a developer, I dream up, try to start, and abandon many&amp;hellip;many projects. When I work occasionally to get these projects out of my head and into code, I will pull on any open source threads I am given. The really cool part about this is I usually end up finding the people who are already trying to do what I am setting out to do.</description></item><item><title>Monopolistic ISPs</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2013/11/09/monopolistic-isps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 09:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2013/11/09/monopolistic-isps/</guid><description>I am on the lowest tier of TWC broadband in NYC and I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m connecting from a third world country. For $20 a month I don&amp;rsquo;t expect the fastest internet, but I expect it to be just as reliable as the next persons internet. One thing I&amp;rsquo;m not going to do is pay more to the same people who can&amp;rsquo;t provide decent service in the first place.</description></item><item><title>Look ma, I inspired a webcomic!</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2013/10/23/look-ma-i-inspired-a-webcomic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 10:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2013/10/23/look-ma-i-inspired-a-webcomic/</guid><description>paircomix: Stop pronouncing my typos!
Never</description></item><item><title>Was Frankenstein('s Monster) a Zombie?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2013/10/08/was-frankenstein-s-monster-a-zombie/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2013/10/08/was-frankenstein-s-monster-a-zombie/</guid><description>The primary definition of a zombie, according to Google is as follows:
a corpse said to be revived by witchcraft, esp. in certain African and Caribbean religions. Early religions lacked the scientific methods to explain everyday events and defaulted to labeling things that couldn&amp;rsquo;t otherwise be explained as witchcraft. It is through that stretch of the definition of a zombie that allow the walkers on AMC&amp;rsquo;s The Walking Dead to be labeled zombies.</description></item></channel></rss>