<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 17:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My AI Story (2/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-21-My-AI-Story-23-e5cf6d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 17:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-21-My-AI-Story-23-e5cf6d/</guid><description>Learning in school was very difficult for me because I was more of a hands on learning and school was very heavy on lecturing. When I have things like that which frustrate me, I try and solve them with technology. This was what I had planned to do with my ed tech company &amp;ldquo;Socrenchus.&amp;rdquo; Before Socrenchus though, I was interning in Mountain View and I got to meet some of the AI great&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>Seitan is a dish best served cold</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 08:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</guid><description>My first kitchen obsession of the quarantine season, was Seitan. The reason being that it is delicious, and I can make it entirely with ingredients shipped via Amazon. While this mostly appeals to me because I didn&amp;rsquo;t much feel like going to the super market, it also helped that I&amp;rsquo;m a huge nerd and I like the idea of creating something out of simple powdered ingredients.
It was a bumpy road to getting it right.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (1/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</guid><description>If I&amp;rsquo;m going to start writing about AI, I figure I should give some backstory first on my life in AI.
My first introduction to AI was probably when I was 9 years old and snuck downstairs to watch the first Matrix movie that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to be watching. This did a great deal to feed what has become an AI obsession over the years.
In high school, after I had been programming on my own for a while with only stack overflow to guide me (plus a couple people who volunteered to help me with my shareware), I started pondering about AI from the perspective of how it worked.</description></item><item><title>Kitchen Experiments: the weirdest way to cook</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</guid><description>As COVID-19 settled in and the outside food procurement grew fraught with uncertainty, I turned to something I managed to avoid for a very long time&amp;hellip; cooking.
My solution to this problem was to geek out on my love of science, minimalism, and efficiency to create tasty, weird, nutritious food that doesn&amp;rsquo;t upset my stomach or other parts of my body. You may be wondering about that last one, but I can assure you, when you start playing with discrete chemical ingredients to make your food, having the wrong combination of foods can lead to a unique experience.</description></item><item><title>A letter to police</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-12-A-letter-to-police-5086c8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 17:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-12-A-letter-to-police-5086c8/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not usually outwardly political, but I have something to get off my chest. I recently overheard a police officer talking about how it won&amp;rsquo;t be worth it if he has to get insurance so he won&amp;rsquo;t get sued. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable enough to get into a debate with him, which later made me even more uncomfortable, so I will address the issue here.
When you signed up to be a public servant and put yourself in harms way to protect your community, it was one of the noblest and bravest things you could do.</description></item><item><title>New Landing Page - New Commitment</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-11-new-landing-page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-11-new-landing-page/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to redo my landing page in response to a realization that I need to sell myself a bit better. While this post isn&amp;rsquo;t related to the topics tagged above, it is a placeholder for my commitment to put some more effort into publishing here.</description></item><item><title>Quarantine Rule #2: Play Video Games</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-09-video-games/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-09-video-games/</guid><description>While we are physically isolated from each-other, we are missing the ability to go out and make new experiences with the people we care about as well as spontaneous experiences with people we&amp;rsquo;ve never seen before.
We are all connected with each-other via the internet, but the internet lacks the richness of experiences that you get in the real world. While this is true to some degree, if you dive into the world of video games, you will quickly realize that it can provide some pretty incredible experiences that make you forget you are at home in your apartment.</description></item><item><title>Quarantine Rule #1: Exercise every day</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-workout/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-workout/</guid><description>It may sound like a lot, but if you are like me and your quarantine space is limited to a studio apartment, then it is probably the most essential thing you can do to stay sane. The three groups of exercise I alternate between are:
Anaerobic Aerobic Stretching As an experienced introvert, it may not come as a surprise to you that exercise is one of the things I tend to go long periods neglecting, but in this new COVID-19 world, I decided it was mission critical so I went on a YouTube research quest to figure out what I was going to do for exercise.</description></item><item><title>Quarantine Tips from Experienced Introvert</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-life/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-life/</guid><description>The year is 2003. It is a lovely spring day and I can see out my window where the trees and birds sing. Then a yell comes from downstairs, it is my mother telling me it is so nice out I should come outside. The temptation is strong, but the draw of my new computer that I had been obsessing over is even stronger.
Fast-forward to 2020. COVID-19 terrorizes the world and we are all forced to quarantine until god knows when.</description></item><item><title>High Altitude Mass Volley</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2019-08-07-high-altitude-mass-volley/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2019-08-07-high-altitude-mass-volley/</guid><description>Preamble I have always been interested in space, but this idea for getting there cheaper has been brewing for a few years, and while I’ve yet to sit down and do the math, it has gotten to a place where it seems intuitive enough to work.
Before I go into the solution, let’s look at the problem. At present, out best way of getting to space involves stacking explosives as high as we can, sitting on top with a countdown, and hoping that we planned for all the eventualities.</description></item><item><title>The Dangers of Idiomatic Programming</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-12-07-idiom-shmidiom/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-12-07-idiom-shmidiom/</guid><description>What does it mean to be idiomatic?
&amp;ldquo;Of, relating to, or conforming to idiom&amp;rdquo; - Merriam-Webster
So what is an idiom?
&amp;ldquo;The syntactical, grammatical, or structural form peculiar to a language&amp;rdquo; - Merriam-Webster
When we talk about idiomatic programming, we are talking about doing things because it is &amp;ldquo;the way&amp;rdquo; to do them, or because so-and-so says this is a rule that can’t be broken.
Why is it important to see past these idioms and understand why they are &amp;ldquo;the way?</description></item><item><title>The Job of an OS</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-06-job-of-os/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-06-job-of-os/</guid><description>It started with a gitter chat then a tweet, followed by a blog post.
&amp;hellip;
Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some time to digest my thoughts, and I think it is time for, a second blog post.
Whenever I think something needs redefining, the first thing I like to do is look for a definition (shocking right?). The Merriam-Webster dictionary defines and Operating System as:
Software that controls the operation of a computer and directs the processing of programs (as by assigning storage space in memory and controlling input and output functions)</description></item><item><title>Why are operating systems still multi-user?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-05-multi-user-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-11-05-multi-user-systems/</guid><description>So I&amp;rsquo;m minding my own business, setting up Arch linux in my unrooted Termux installation on my phone, when all of a sudden, makepkg wants me to not be root to run a build. Excuse me? What century are we in?
Let me clarify, when I am running linux in a container to build applications the operating system should not be bothering me with arbitrary user systems.
When was the last time you logged into a multi-user unix system that had other users on it?</description></item><item><title>Future of Flight: Spontaneous trip to Paris</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-10-17-future-airplanes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2017-10-17-future-airplanes/</guid><description>I want to go to France, I didn&amp;rsquo;t plan to go, I was just waking on the highline and was like, I think I want to go to Paris. I take out my phone, and open my air travel app and put in Paris. It tells me how much it costs, and I click accept. It takes me to a border patrol and security flow where I need to answer some lame questions, but it isn&amp;rsquo;t so bad.</description></item><item><title>Crystallize your abstractions carefully...</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2016/06/21/crystallize-carfully/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 01:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2016/06/21/crystallize-carfully/</guid><description>For as long as I&amp;rsquo;ve been a developer I have been reminded of the rule of three for refactoring and every time I hear it, I die a little inside.
If building a new abstraction is so painful, that it is easier to copy and paste large chunks of code, you need to rethink the way you are building your abstractions. Building the right abstractions isn&amp;rsquo;t just a time consuming distraction from building software, it is software engineering.</description></item><item><title>Imaginary Lines</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2016/04/01/imaginary-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2016/04/01/imaginary-lines/</guid><description>If I had to sum up the job of a software engineer in laymen&amp;rsquo;s terms, I would tell you that we draw imaginary lines around imaginary concepts until those concepts can map to both a specific set of instructions for a machine and a common understanding for programmers.
Why am I stating the obvious? Well, it is quite simply to emphasize just how important it is where we draw those lines.</description></item><item><title>GraphiQL Bookmarklet</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/12/19/graphiql-bookmarklet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 13:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/12/19/graphiql-bookmarklet/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure most of you, if you have done any work with graphql, have heard of graphiql. It is an indespensible tool for writing and testing graphql queries.
The problem is that now that I&amp;rsquo;m not using express at the moment. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to go through the trouble of trying to fit graphiql into my stack.
To solve it, a graphiql bookmarklet: Enjoy!</description></item><item><title>jscodemigrate (deps|dependencies)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/12/11/jscodemigrate-deps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 00:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/12/11/jscodemigrate-deps/</guid><description>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet read about jscodemigrate, read about it here. If you already know about jscodemigrate then stick around because there is a new feature, and it is ready for you to use, just npm install jscodemigrate@latest --save-dev.
You already know that you can run all of your jscodeshift scripts at once and easily maintain your project with a directory full of timestamped codemods, but now, you can make it easy for those who depend on your npm packages to respond quickly to your API changes.</description></item><item><title>jscodeshift + rails migrations = jscodemigrate</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/12/05/jscodemigrate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 00:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/12/05/jscodemigrate/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on lots of projects big and small, but as time went on they all suffered from the same problem. Changing standards and updated api&amp;rsquo;s left code fragmented as the codebase grew.
From the time I started working on coffeelint, the problem has been stewing in my head. Subconciously on the lookout for a solution, I heard about codemods. Let me preface by saying I&amp;rsquo;ve been quite obsessed with everything facebook engineering has been doing in open source lately.</description></item><item><title>Graphql + Bookshelf</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/08/13/graphql-bookshelf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 00:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/08/13/graphql-bookshelf/</guid><description>I recently switched over the project I was working on from MongoDB to PostgreSQL. The reason for the switch is not what I&amp;rsquo;m writing to discuss, but I&amp;rsquo;ll just say that the unpredictability of mongodb was starting to become an issue in development. The thought was that if it was already difficult before the data starts pouring in, it will probably be a nightmare one the product is in use. And that meant switching from graffiti-mongoose, to my own graphql database glue.</description></item><item><title>React Native on Heroku</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/07/26/react-native-on-heroku/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/07/26/react-native-on-heroku/</guid><description>As a web developer doing iOS development with react native, I need a staging environment for the product manager to review changes to the app.
On the web, that means using Heroku, but with a react native app it is a bit more complicated.
My react native app has two components, the packager (for serving the client code) and the server (for interacting with the app).
Heroku only lets one process bind to an external port, so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy to do without creating two heroku apps.</description></item><item><title>Will Relay replace Flux?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/07/25/relay-vs-flux/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/07/25/relay-vs-flux/</guid><description>Relay is out in preview! Have a look.
When people talk about Relay they think of it as the server-client link in the Facebook stack, but is that really all it is?
Flux still has a place on the client because you need to manage temporary app state, right?
I think it doesn&amp;rsquo;t. Flux is an architecture for unidirectional data flow that separates out input from the user and the server so that it can react without getting tangled up.</description></item><item><title>Why I'm Excited for Facebook's Relay and GraphQL</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/07/08/why-relay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/07/08/why-relay/</guid><description>Relay is out in preview! Have a look.
I want to tell you in as few words as possible why I am so excited to get my hands on Relay and GraphQL.
React is widely popular because it is simple and declarative, making it very deterministic and easy to work with. React is also fully composable, making it imensly powerful with high potential for writing reusable code.
Relay is a mirror image of React, except instead of composing beautiful views for the web and native mobile devices using JSX, you can compose data from your database for your views using graphql.</description></item><item><title>Bringing back 'Under Construction' in style</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/25/under-construction/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 10:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/25/under-construction/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m just going to go ahead and say what&amp;rsquo;s on everyone&amp;rsquo;s mind already. Where did all those great under construction pages from the 90s go with the animated gifs and text scrolling accross the screen.
Since I know you all missed those pages so much, I brought them back. If you visit any of my websites that I have yet to utilize:
worthy.gift unravel.space solve.technology socrenchus.com stackoverachieve.com stackoverachiever.com You will see an under construction banner that uses HTML5 gradients, text shadow, and of course, a marquee tag.</description></item><item><title>Searching for an Isomorphic Reactiflux Stack</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/17/isomorphic-react-flux-stack/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 10:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/17/isomorphic-react-flux-stack/</guid><description>Now that Relay is out in preview, it will probably replace Flux entirely.
Why React? A few months ago, the release of React Native by Facebook convinced me to make the leap to React.
I spent a while working on a React Native app and quickly learned that I needed to bring in Flux. After watching a few videos and reading a few blogs, I added my own implementation of flux to my react native app.</description></item><item><title>Back to the blog...</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/11/back-to-the-blog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 01:19:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/11/back-to-the-blog/</guid><description>Now I know this isn&amp;rsquo;t my first time promising more blog time but I&amp;rsquo;m renewing my vows.
I&amp;rsquo;m not going to be so rigid with my every day blog promise, but I will make an effort where possible. Also, I plan on doing something which I haven&amp;rsquo;t done before which is try to keep my blog posts up to date.
If you go back through my blog posts you will see edits and updates to make sure I can stay proud of my blog instead of being unconfident of stale blog posts.</description></item><item><title>Switched to Jekyll!</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/05/switched-to-jekyll/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 10:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/05/switched-to-jekyll/</guid><description>Just switched my blog to Jekyll because it is easier to manage. I will probably continue using tumblr here and there to reblog interesting things, but not to write my posts.
Also didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like deleting the intro post, so here it is&amp;hellip;
You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</description></item><item><title>Minimalist? or just boring?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/03/minimalist-or-just-boring/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 17:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/03/minimalist-or-just-boring/</guid><description>
&lt;blockquote>&lt;strong>EDIT:&lt;/strong> Blog is now on Jekyll and has replaced main website, katamari is playable on any blog page so no fake text is needed.&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>I consider myself a pretty minimalist individual. I follow the time tested principles of YAGNI and build my systems in small, single purpose components.&lt;/p>&lt;p>I’ve had a very simple website for quite some time now. All it has is my name and a list of social media / web profile links. When I look at it, I see simplicity, but I began to fear that when others look at it, they see &lt;b>boring.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&lt;blockquote>&lt;p>Try it out at&lt;/p>&lt;p>&lt;b>&lt;a href="http://www.brysgo.com">http://www.brysgo.com&lt;/a>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>&lt;figure class="tmblr-full" data-orig-height="1185" data-orig-width="1247">&lt;img src="https://40.media.tumblr.com/ec75fd19a4ffd14cd85ca11f6fac5a1c/tumblr_inline_npe6bchsee1r60sb8_540.png" data-orig-height="1185" data-orig-width="1247"/>&lt;/figure></description></item><item><title>Avoiding Tunnel Vision</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/02/avoiding-tunnel-vision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 18:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/06/02/avoiding-tunnel-vision/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
This is a blog post to advocate for something that is generally frowned upon
in software development. If you want to join the angry crowd and throw rotten
tomatoes, you are welcome to.
&lt;/p>
&lt;figure data-orig-width="480" data-orig-height="360" class="tmblr-full">
&lt;img
src="https://36.media.tumblr.com/16e1827841b75b6bd61488f880867af3/tumblr_inline_npca0h9cHd1r60sb8_540.jpg"
data-orig-width="480"
data-orig-height="360"
/>
&lt;/figure></description></item><item><title>Wishlist: Chromebook search/ctrl</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/04/29/chromebook-search-ctrl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 15:11:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/04/29/chromebook-search-ctrl/</guid><description>In order to do development on my Chromebook, I need to change the search key to a control key. Problem is the search key is really sexy, and while I can make the control key the search key, it just isn&amp;rsquo;t the same. Also, sometimes I actually try and use Ctrl like a control key and everything is wonky.
So here is my request. I want to be able to set the search key to bring up the search if I haven’t pressed any keys in combination with it, but if I have, it should act like a control key.</description></item><item><title>2015 Chromebook Pixel</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/04/29/2015-chromebook-pixel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 15:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/04/29/2015-chromebook-pixel/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
I just got a Chromebook pixel today and it is gorgeous. It embodies simplicity
and minimalism while still being completely functional.
&lt;/p>
&lt;figure class="tmblr-full" data-orig-height="2506" data-orig-width="2306">
&lt;img
src="https://41.media.tumblr.com/3ba69eaeab41e5c7ee1983168c747e9c/tumblr_inline_nnl0vc6MnW1r60sb8_540.jpg"
data-orig-height="2506"
data-orig-width="2306"
/>
&lt;/figure></description></item><item><title>Web Development on a Nexus 9</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/03/11/web-development-on-a-nexus-9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/03/11/web-development-on-a-nexus-9/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
I recently did something a little crazy. I am a professional web developer,
and I decided I was going to move all of my development to the cloud. This
paradigm that has brought so much convenience into every corner of my life was
going to close the final gap. It took me a little while, but I have 99%
percent of what I had going on my Macbook Pro, so here is my setup.
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Giving 1-π/4 of your wealth to charity</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/14/giving-1-4-of-your-wealth-to-charity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/14/giving-1-4-of-your-wealth-to-charity/</guid><description>
&lt;p>&lt;span>As a New Yorker, I often feel guilty for how filthy it is and how there are people who have to live on our filthy streets.&lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;span>I try to give (not on the street) like a good person, but I always feel like it isn’t enough. So I did what I do everyday and attempted to solve my problems with emotionless calculations.&lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;span>I’m not super religious, but the first place I look when I’m in a moral dilemma is to my religion. I vaguely remember from pre-school that one of the commandments (the extended version) instructs us to leave the corners of our fields.&lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;span>Here comes the math. The area of a circle, the shape used to plow a field, is πr^&lt;/span>&lt;span>2&lt;/span>&lt;span> and the formula for a square (the presumed average shape of a field) is x^&lt;/span>&lt;span>2&lt;/span>&lt;span>.&lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;span>&lt;img src="https://31.media.tumblr.com/769ec843225540e5a8cd57427af73d20/tumblr_inline_ni70sty2sf1r60sb8.jpg"/>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;span></description></item><item><title>The Seesaw First Five Days</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/09/the-seesaw-first-five-days/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 17:57:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/09/the-seesaw-first-five-days/</guid><description>The Seesaw First Five Daysfrancinegoldsteinmarketblog:
January 8, 2015
Happy new year! Volatility is alive and well!
Let’s recap the first five days: the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index sold off 2.7% for the first three days and then surged 3.0% for the next two days.
The sharp stock market volatility has proved especially challenging for all but the nimblest&amp;hellip;
Thanks for the advice, seems like a fairly low risk / low maintenance way to maintain a portfolio.</description></item><item><title>18 Years of Crohn's, 1 Week of Soylent 1.3</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/03/18-years-of-crohns-1-week-of-soylent-1-3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2015 12:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/03/18-years-of-crohns-1-week-of-soylent-1-3/</guid><description>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>
&lt;strong>UPDATE:&lt;/strong> The nutritionist suggested I stop soylent after
version 1.4 made me irregular and wasn't helping me keep on weight. 1.5
looks better but I am going to wait a little before diving back in.
&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Here is a quick synopsis of my case&amp;hellip;&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>
&lt;em
>I was diagnosed with Crohn&amp;rsquo;s disease when I was 7 years old. I have
managed to avoid surgery, but was a frequent flyer in the emergency room
for flare ups. I was on remicade for about ten years and have been on
mercaptopurine and mesalamine since I was diagnosed. I was
on antibiotics from the time I was diagnosed until I graduated college,
and somewhere in that span I was briefly on growth hormones and steroids.
Additionally, I am most recently back on antibiotics and budesonide.&lt;/em
>
&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>
My most recent flare up a few months ago is what put me on budesonide and a
few weeks before I started soylent I went back on antibiotics (tinidazole and
ciprofloxacin). I ordered soylent months ago and was delighted when Soylent
V1.3 arrived in the midst of me trying to control my symptoms.</description></item><item><title>Teaspoon with Capybara-Webkit</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/02/teaspoon-with-capybara-webkit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2015/01/02/teaspoon-with-capybara-webkit/</guid><description>Do you use teaspoon to run your javascript tests? Do you use Capybara-Webkitto run your feature tests? Now you can run your teaspoon suite faster without having to install and boot up phantomjs. Just use the new Capybara-Webkit driver for teaspoon!You may also have more success with it on your CI server, as that is what caused us to make this change.</description></item><item><title>Linearly dependant Rspec 'behavior'</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/31/linearly-dependant-rspec-behavior/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/31/linearly-dependant-rspec-behavior/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
&lt;strong>The problem:&lt;/strong> You finish writing your test in rspec, and after
you have carefully described the scenario, you go to write your next test. For
your next test you need to check that after you do everything for the first
test, the next thing doesn’t break.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Potential hacks:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
a) Well, it is just this one time, I can ignore the description of the spec
and just throw in another assertion after my test.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
While you’re at it, why don’t you just do everything in one test, I’m sure
you’ll be able to figure it out when it fails.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
b) There isn’t that much setup, I can just do the same thing I did in the last
test as setup!
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Lets pretend we don’t care about performance, I hope we can guarantee that the
first test won’t change and that the setup state of the second test won’t get
out of touch with reality!
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>But wait, there’s another solutions…&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p></description></item><item><title>How-to : Submit your Tumblr blog sitemap to Google Webmaster tools</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/30/how-to-submit-your-tumblr-blog-sitemap-to-google/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 19:04:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/30/how-to-submit-your-tumblr-blog-sitemap-to-google/</guid><description> How-to : Submit your Tumblr blog sitemap to Google Webmaster toolsaepearson:
A friend of mine, Paul, asked me today about how he may go about submitting a sitemap to Google Webmaster tools for his Tumblr blog.
I found the surprisingly simple solution!
1 - First, you’ll need to sign up for Google Webmaster Tools:
http://www.google.com/webmasters/
2 - Now you’ll&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Wishlist: Google Calendar Trips</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/23/wishlist-google-calendar-trips/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 15:24:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/23/wishlist-google-calendar-trips/</guid><description>Google calendar has many features I rely on, one of my favorites is the integration with Google now that helps you get where you need to go on time.
I use the to make sure I always leave time for the subway. However, sometimes my trips are a little longer. Google already knows when I&amp;rsquo;m going on a flight, why not add trips to my calendar.
If I&amp;rsquo;m going on a train to long island two hours of my time are spent on the train.</description></item><item><title>Contextualizing with DSLs</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/19/contextualizing-with-dsls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 18:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/19/contextualizing-with-dsls/</guid><description>Why do we use domain specific languages? My first reaction to them when I started programming in the real world was to scorn them with the attitude that they introduce unnecessary complication for both the developer and the computer. What good could they possibly do? Like any programmer thrown into a stack, I faithfully used the established patterns, knowing that any divergence from the standard usually has a much worse effect than dealing with it.</description></item><item><title>Use your YAML fixtures as documentation</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/10/use-your-yaml-fixtures-as-documentation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/10/use-your-yaml-fixtures-as-documentation/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
If you are writing an API sandbox with a local development tool, you will no
doubt need fixtures for your API’s modeling.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
It turns out those fixtures are a great example of how your API is modeled. If
you comment on those fixtures, they can be great documentation for the
perusing developer.</description></item><item><title>Voltrb first impressions</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/04/voltrb-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 23:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/04/voltrb-first-impressions/</guid><description>
&lt;p>What do you get when you cross meteorjs with rails?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The answer is quite simply, voltrb.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Getting started is not quite as easy as meteor or rails, which isn’t
surprising considering how fresh it is.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
So far I built a search box that creates new items on submit, but searches
through existing items as you type. I’m building the site that will go here:
&lt;a href="http://www.procedur.al">http://www.procedur.al&lt;/a>.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
I love how you get default models and collections for each storage method and
you can optionally create models that are autoloaded if they exist. This
reminds me if ember, only I don’t have to leave ruby!</description></item><item><title>The wonderful distributed world wide web!</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/01/the-wonderful-distributed-world-wide-web/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 23:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/12/01/the-wonderful-distributed-world-wide-web/</guid><description>…umm, I mean let’s all use the same service so we don’t have to manage or own hardware. There are advantages and disadvantages to distributing the internet. One of the advantages initially were that it was the only way to host anything. There were no easy services for sharing content. There are of course many other advantages to the distribution of the internet, like fault tolerance, but those were quickly forgotten.</description></item><item><title>Commit to a single way</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/26/commit-to-a-single-way/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 13:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/26/commit-to-a-single-way/</guid><description>Software engineers are responsible for adding new and unforeseen complexity to established, carefully thought out systems. It tends to be a reflex when told to add complexity, that we special case the complexity and fall through to the system you had before. This works in many cases and is great if the complexity being added is a footnote that you don&amp;rsquo;t intend to come back to. Complexity that is essential to the long term success of your product needs to be &amp;ldquo;native.</description></item><item><title>Strategies for reviewing massive pull requests</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/20/strategies-for-reviewing-massive-pull-requests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/20/strategies-for-reviewing-massive-pull-requests/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
Too many massive pull requests are a smell, but sometimes big pull requests
are a necessity. It is easy to come across a large pull request and
immediately reject it, but you shouldn’t be intimidated by the size of a PR.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Your first job when reviewing such a PR is to identify why it is so large. Is
there a large piece of functionality being added or Is a common pattern in the
code being changed? Maybe the pull request is a large feature combined with
pattern changes.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
If it is the third, I would definitely ask for the PR to be broken up. There
is no reason to do a pattern change and new feature in one PR. Otherwise the
actions you take will depend largely on what the reason for the PR’s size is.</description></item><item><title>Why is consistency in code so difficult?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/19/why-is-consistency-in-code-so-difficult/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/19/why-is-consistency-in-code-so-difficult/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
Why is it we can’t just agree on a pattern to use when programming and get
everything done already?
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
The fact is that while language level stylistic differences are very easy to
agree on, the patterns in which you use the tools provided by the language
emerge proportional to the size of the system.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
So you can come to a new pattern, agree on it, come to the next, agree on it,
etc… but there will always be more patterns.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Okay well, we can’t agree on patterns, at least we can agree on philosophies
for coming up with new patterns?</description></item><item><title>A RoseFactory by any other name...</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/18/a-rosefactory-by-any-other-name/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 22:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/18/a-rosefactory-by-any-other-name/</guid><description>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>
There are only two hard things in Computer Science: cache invalidation and
naming things.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>— Phil Karlton&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>
Lets hold on to cache invalidation for another post&lt;a
href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g-4-gLlF0uw"
>…&lt;/a
>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Naming things (or should I say labeling them&lt;a
href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g-4-gLlF0uw"
>…&lt;/a
>) is a very hard problem.
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>Why is it a hard problem?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>
Consider this, imagine you are building a piece of IKEA furniture. You get all
the pieces in the box and you have to put them together. Now imagine that all
the pieces had a succinct description that you used to put them together. Now
imagine that you couldn’t see or feel the pieces and all you had to work with
were these descriptions.
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;img
alt=""
src="http://photos1.blogger.com/blogger2/1715/1669/1600/larson-oct-1987.gif"
/>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p></description></item><item><title>UX that grows complexity with the user, not the product</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/ux-that-grows-complexity-with-the-user-not-the/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/ux-that-grows-complexity-with-the-user-not-the/</guid><description>
&lt;p>
Have you ever played a videogame where you sit down, turn on the game, and are
overwhelmed with a thousand cool things you can do?*
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>NO&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Why not? Because that game company went out of business long ago. Games start
with one thing the user can do, waits until the user is comfortable, then
introduces the next thing.</description></item><item><title>Blogs on blogs on blogs</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/if-i-write-a-blog-in-the-forest-does-it-make-a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 13:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/if-i-write-a-blog-in-the-forest-does-it-make-a/</guid><description>I’ve decided to write a blog post every day, even if it is crappy. Why? Is it so I can feel important? Maybe, but I would never admit that. The reason I’m sticking to is that I want to get better at reflecting on important parts of my day. It may help me appreciate all the interesting things I come across daily that are quickly relegated to a distant memory.</description></item><item><title>OO code isn't spaghetti proof</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/oo-code-isnt-spaghetti-proof/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 02:11:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/15/oo-code-isnt-spaghetti-proof/</guid><description>Today I had another terrifying, tear swallowing pull request moment. It involved clearly abstracted pieces of our system being clearly and purposefully coupled. If this doesn&amp;rsquo;t bring you to your knees let me try and illustrate why this is so bad. You are the kind of developer that pardon my french, &amp;ldquo;gets shit done.&amp;rdquo; Because you are such a doer, you connect the first input with the desired output.</description></item><item><title>Ink/filepicker-rails doesn't preview my unsupported image format</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/13/ink-filepicker-rails-doesnt-preview-my/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 19:30:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/11/13/ink-filepicker-rails-doesnt-preview-my/</guid><description>First, before you go any further&amp;hellip; check to make sure the image you&amp;rsquo;re trying isn&amp;rsquo;t just broken. I visited the image in the browser and realized that the browser supported the format, so the broken preview had to be somewhere in filepicker. In my case I was using a(n) .ico file and since filepicker.io only supports post processing on .jpg and .pngI had to come up with a work around.</description></item><item><title>Soylent mission one</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/08/19/this-is-the-first-thing-im-going-to-try-when-i/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 10:46:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/08/19/this-is-the-first-thing-im-going-to-try-when-i/</guid><description>UPDATE: I got a later version of soylent and used a different recipe and it was yummy. This is the first thing I&amp;rsquo;m going to try when I get my soylent&amp;hellip;
leecaubleblog:
Baked Soylent
This is not my first attempt to bake with Soylent. During beta testing I made a few batches of peanut butter cookies. I made a few mistakes with this batch of brownies but overall the taste and texture are OK.</description></item><item><title>Wishlist: Coding in the Cloud (without falling from the sky)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/07/28/wishlist-coding-in-the-cloud-without-falling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 09:01:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/07/28/wishlist-coding-in-the-cloud-without-falling/</guid><description>As a diehard Google fanboy, it is my duty to figure out how I can switch to a Chromebook as my primary laptop. The only way I can see myself doing that is if I were provided a web based programming experience that was better than coding on metal.
Enter Bryan&amp;rsquo;s fantasy world, where a flourishing space economy affords us with cheap vacations to the moon and once a year visits to grandma on the mars colony.</description></item><item><title>Wishlist Series</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/07/27/wishlist-series/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 21:55:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/07/27/wishlist-series/</guid><description>Those of you who know me already know I am a man of many wishes and dreams. That means as a developer, I dream up, try to start, and abandon many&amp;hellip;many projects. When I work occasionally to get these projects out of my head and into code, I will pull on any open source threads I am given. The really cool part about this is I usually end up finding the people who are already trying to do what I am setting out to do.</description></item><item><title>Bye CVS</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2014/05/09/my-breakup-with-cvs-after-7-years-of-patronage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 19:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2014/05/09/my-breakup-with-cvs-after-7-years-of-patronage/</guid><description>I was about to leave a scathing review of the CVS on east 72nd and 2nd, including the manager, Marc, when I read a little bit about how CVS treats it’s employees like crap and I decided against it.
The only thing that keeps me coming back to the place is that I have a really nice pharmacist named Bobby. I wish I could take him with me when I go somewhere else, but I know I can’t.</description></item><item><title>Machine Learning in Go</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2013/11/23/machine-learning-in-go/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 21:53:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2013/11/23/machine-learning-in-go/</guid><description>For a while now I have been curious about Go. There doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be much to it, but it is getting more and more popular. Another itch I&amp;rsquo;ve had for a really long time is to write my own machine learning/AI framework. After looking at Golang a bit more, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t shake the feeling that it would be the perfect language for my machine learning framework. I did some searching and while there were people talking about writing machine learning frameworks in Go, no one was actually doing it.</description></item><item><title>Monopolistic ISPs</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2013/11/09/monopolistic-isps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 09:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2013/11/09/monopolistic-isps/</guid><description>I am on the lowest tier of TWC broadband in NYC and I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m connecting from a third world country. For $20 a month I don&amp;rsquo;t expect the fastest internet, but I expect it to be just as reliable as the next persons internet. One thing I&amp;rsquo;m not going to do is pay more to the same people who can&amp;rsquo;t provide decent service in the first place.</description></item><item><title>Look ma, I inspired a webcomic!</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2013/10/23/look-ma-i-inspired-a-webcomic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 10:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2013/10/23/look-ma-i-inspired-a-webcomic/</guid><description>paircomix: Stop pronouncing my typos!
Never</description></item><item><title>Was Frankenstein('s Monster) a Zombie?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/2013/10/08/was-frankenstein-s-monster-a-zombie/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/2013/10/08/was-frankenstein-s-monster-a-zombie/</guid><description>The primary definition of a zombie, according to Google is as follows:
a corpse said to be revived by witchcraft, esp. in certain African and Caribbean religions. Early religions lacked the scientific methods to explain everyday events and defaulted to labeling things that couldn&amp;rsquo;t otherwise be explained as witchcraft. It is through that stretch of the definition of a zombie that allow the walkers on AMC&amp;rsquo;s The Walking Dead to be labeled zombies.</description></item></channel></rss>