<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>backstory on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/backstory/</link><description>Recent content in backstory on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 08:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/backstory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>coming soon: peerstate</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-06-coming-soon-peersta-415acc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 08:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-06-coming-soon-peersta-415acc/</guid><description>All of my open source projects start with trying to build something, getting frustrated, saying in my head &amp;ldquo;I wish I could just do this,&amp;rdquo; then obsessively investigating what it would take to be able to &amp;ldquo;just do this.&amp;rdquo;
Sometimes this inspiration comes on a work project, but more often, it comes when I am working on a side project, or playing with some new open source thing. My first example of such a project, was when I was working on an investment project called Herd.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (3/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-26-My-AI-Story-33-11a67c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-26-My-AI-Story-33-11a67c/</guid><description>After graduating with my BS in Computer Science, AI moved to side project status as I took a job as a Full Stack Software Engineer at Pivotal Labs. The side project years of my AI life made slow progress. I managed to play with some algorithms that one time when I was trying to learn golang. I eventually implemented my logic gate pool genetic algorithm as part of a more ambitions side project I called thoughtnet.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (2/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-21-My-AI-Story-23-e5cf6d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 17:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-21-My-AI-Story-23-e5cf6d/</guid><description>Learning in school was very difficult for me because I was more of a hands on learner and school was very heavy on lecturing. When I am in situations that frustrate me, I try and solve them with technology. This was what I had planned to do with my ed tech company &amp;ldquo;Socrenchus.&amp;rdquo; Before Socrenchus though, I was interning in Mountain View and I got to meet some of the AI great&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (1/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</guid><description>If I&amp;rsquo;m going to start writing about AI, I figure I should give some backstory first on my life in AI.
My first introduction to AI was probably when I was 9 years old and snuck downstairs to watch the first Matrix movie that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to be watching. This did a great deal to feed what has become an AI obsession over the years.
In high school, after I had been programming on my own for a while with only stack overflow to guide me (plus a couple people who volunteered to help me with my shareware), I started pondering about AI from the perspective of how it worked.</description></item></channel></rss>