<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>none on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/categories/none/</link><description>Recent content in none on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 08:05:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/categories/none/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is life?</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-10-08-What-is-life-7c954f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 08:05:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-10-08-What-is-life-7c954f/</guid><description>After googling the definition of Life and I was a bit disappointed to find that the best definitions were anchored in functions we associate with life, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite put my finger on why this made me sad.
&amp;ldquo;the condition that distinguishes animals and plants from inorganic matter, including the capacity for growth, reproduction, functional activity, and continual change preceding death.&amp;rdquo;
Setting aside the use of a word to define itself (in this case &amp;ldquo;animals and plants&amp;rdquo; are synonymous with life and &amp;ldquo;inorganic&amp;rdquo; is just another way of saying &amp;ldquo;not living.</description></item><item><title>$trong AI</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-09-10-dollartrong-AI-f769ed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 08:05:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-09-10-dollartrong-AI-f769ed/</guid><description>When it was announced not too long ago, GPT-3 set a new standard for the size of an AI model at a whopping 175 billion parameters, and an estimated cost of at least $4.6 million. Ever since the first closed beta examples started showing up, it has been blowing people&amp;rsquo;s minds and causing everyone to think about what is next.
One of the best things about programming (and open source in particular) is that everyone can play and have access to everything they need to build cool stuff.</description></item><item><title>End of Work = Beginning of Creativity</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-19-End-of-Work-Beginnin-75f8b0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 08:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-19-End-of-Work-Beginnin-75f8b0/</guid><description>When most people hear the end of work, they might picture the world looking glazed over and staring at the television with a bag of cheese puffs in their hand making an occasional nasal laugh. So why am I so excited for the end of work?
The reason is that while I do believe the future will be that way for some, I think the vast majority will have a much different experience.</description></item><item><title>Vegan Insomnia Beef in Ginger Sauce</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-16-Vegan-Insomnia-Beef-cc6199/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 17:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-16-Vegan-Insomnia-Beef-cc6199/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going back and forth for a little while with my sister about trying to recreate a seitan ginger beef dish from a restaurant that we like in Vermont. It is a little tricky for me since I&amp;rsquo;ve never done a seitan beef before and because of the whole low FODMAP thing, but I finally decided to give it a try. After substituting pretty much every ingredient in the recipes I found, I finally created what I lovingly refer to as insomnia beef, since I associate eating it with not being the least bit tired (probably because of the high protein content and the cocoa nibs I threw in).</description></item><item><title>GitHub Inbox Zero</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-14-GitHub-Inbox-Zero-9892d6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 08:04:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-14-GitHub-Inbox-Zero-9892d6/</guid><description>I recently reached inbox zero on GitHub for the first time in a long time. A while ago I got freaked out by the possibility of people stealing my secret keys through CI and I disabled my CI tokens on my zillion GitHub repos. It was all broken windows from there. Before I knew it my GitHub was a graveyard of packages with out of date dependencies that I had no time to update.</description></item><item><title>Dumpling Pancakes</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-11-Dumpling-Pancakes-07c1af/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 08:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-11-Dumpling-Pancakes-07c1af/</guid><description>I think it is safe to say that a lot of people like dumplings 🥟- and more safe to say that they are too complicated and time consuming for most people to make themselves (yes, you could order them but that is besides the point). I realized I could make dumplings by dipping the protein in a thick batter instead of wrapping it.
The benefit was this was a little bit easier, however, it still required an action per small food piece.</description></item><item><title>the yin and yang of utility</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-08-the-yin-and-yang-of-dc939a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 17:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-08-the-yin-and-yang-of-dc939a/</guid><description>I just did some dehydrating exercise in the sun, so this will be what amounts to some pontificating shower thoughts. But you already clicked on the link so you might as well read it.
While trying to solve the knapsack problem I got to thinking about the realities of maximizing utility. Since I am a software engineer and engineering is just building tools to maximize utility, I let my mind frolic down that sweet sweet rabbit hole.</description></item><item><title>coming soon: peerstate</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-06-coming-soon-peersta-415acc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 08:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-06-coming-soon-peersta-415acc/</guid><description>All of my open source projects start with trying to build something, getting frustrated, saying in my head &amp;ldquo;I wish I could just do this,&amp;rdquo; then obsessively investigating what it would take to be able to &amp;ldquo;just do this.&amp;rdquo;
Sometimes this inspiration comes on a work project, but more often, it comes when I am working on a side project, or playing with some new open source thing. My first example of such a project, was when I was working on an investment project called Herd.</description></item><item><title>Health Pro's and Con's of Cooking with Discrete Ingredients</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-03-Health-Pros-and-Con-d615f2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 08:04:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-03-Health-Pros-and-Con-d615f2/</guid><description>Remember when I mentioned that cooking with discrete ingredients has side effects? Well, in reality, all food has side effects, they are just drowned out by the popular proportions of everything that are hard coded into the common foods that everyone eats.
When you start experimenting with specific ingredients, you throw that all away. Suddenly, you will find yourself rapidly trying to diagnose something with Google and fix it with another ingredient that you normally eat all the time.</description></item><item><title>Open Source: Chasing the Dream</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-31-Open-Source-Chasing-997a1e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 17:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-31-Open-Source-Chasing-997a1e/</guid><description>I love open source. I love to imagine writing code a certain way, trying to find something that does it, failing to find said thing and building it. I love publishing it and watching people use it. I don&amp;rsquo;t love maintaining it, I don&amp;rsquo;t love the thought of having to improve it with the responsibility involved with making sure those improvements don&amp;rsquo;t break anything for anyone using your thing in a way you didn&amp;rsquo;t intend it to be used.</description></item><item><title>Holding in the Idea Vomit</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-29-Holding-in-the-Idea-1541f1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 08:04:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-29-Holding-in-the-Idea-1541f1/</guid><description>Yesterday I had an idea. Congratulations me, now there are two options, I can:
Take the red pill - see how deep the rabbit hole goes Take the blue pill - be blissfully ignorant of whether my new idea will work The free spirit I am, has lots of trouble with #2 because I am insatiably curious and hate myself. But I recognize that I need to learn how to do this, or I will spend my life jumping from rabbit hole to rabbit hole like a prairie dog.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (3/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-26-My-AI-Story-33-11a67c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-26-My-AI-Story-33-11a67c/</guid><description>After graduating with my BS in Computer Science, AI moved to side project status as I took a job as a Full Stack Software Engineer at Pivotal Labs. The side project years of my AI life made slow progress. I managed to play with some algorithms that one time when I was trying to learn golang. I eventually implemented my logic gate pool genetic algorithm as part of a more ambitions side project I called thoughtnet.</description></item><item><title>project review time</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-24-project-review-time-1a1913/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 08:04:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-24-project-review-time-1a1913/</guid><description>I recently got a good review at work and it helped me start to course correct a dangerous internal narrative. For the last year of projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been on, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard: &amp;ldquo;you are a genius, but you have to work on your communication&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; which in my brain translates to &amp;ldquo;we need to soften the blow of this feedback, but you are a piece of shit to work with&amp;rdquo;
Truth is, when you hear something enough times, you start to believe it.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (2/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-21-My-AI-Story-23-e5cf6d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 17:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-21-My-AI-Story-23-e5cf6d/</guid><description>Learning in school was very difficult for me because I was more of a hands on learner and school was very heavy on lecturing. When I am in situations that frustrate me, I try and solve them with technology. This was what I had planned to do with my ed tech company &amp;ldquo;Socrenchus.&amp;rdquo; Before Socrenchus though, I was interning in Mountain View and I got to meet some of the AI great&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>Seitan is a dish best served cold</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 08:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</guid><description>My first kitchen obsession of the quarantine season, was Seitan. The reason being that it is delicious, and I can make it entirely with ingredients shipped via Amazon. While this mostly appeals to me because I didn&amp;rsquo;t much feel like going to the super market, it also helped that I&amp;rsquo;m a huge nerd and I like the idea of creating something out of simple powdered ingredients.
It was a bumpy road to getting it right.</description></item><item><title>My AI Story (1/3)</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-16-My-AI-Story-13-e86392/</guid><description>If I&amp;rsquo;m going to start writing about AI, I figure I should give some backstory first on my life in AI.
My first introduction to AI was probably when I was 9 years old and snuck downstairs to watch the first Matrix movie that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to be watching. This did a great deal to feed what has become an AI obsession over the years.
In high school, after I had been programming on my own for a while with only stack overflow to guide me (plus a couple people who volunteered to help me with my shareware), I started pondering about AI from the perspective of how it worked.</description></item><item><title>Kitchen Experiments: the weirdest way to cook</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</guid><description>As COVID-19 settled in and the outside food procurement grew fraught with uncertainty, I turned to something I managed to avoid for a very long time&amp;hellip; cooking.
My solution to this problem was to geek out on my love of science, minimalism, and efficiency to create tasty, weird, nutritious food that doesn&amp;rsquo;t upset my stomach or other parts of my body. You may be wondering about that last one, but I can assure you, when you start playing with discrete chemical ingredients to make your food, having the wrong combination of foods can lead to a unique experience.</description></item><item><title>A letter to police</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-12-A-letter-to-police-5086c8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 17:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-12-A-letter-to-police-5086c8/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not usually outwardly political, but I have something to get off my chest. I recently overheard a police officer talking about how it won&amp;rsquo;t be worth it if he has to get insurance so he won&amp;rsquo;t get sued. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable enough to get into a debate with him, which later made me even more uncomfortable, so I will address the issue here.
When you signed up to be a public servant and put yourself in harms way to protect your community, it was one of the noblest and bravest things you could do.</description></item></channel></rss>