<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wishlist on BRYSGO</title><link>http://brysgo.com/tags/wishlist/</link><description>Recent content in wishlist on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 02:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://brysgo.com/tags/wishlist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High Altitude Mass Volley</title><link>http://brysgo.com/post/2019-08-07-high-altitude-mass-volley/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/post/2019-08-07-high-altitude-mass-volley/</guid><description>Preamble I have always been interested in space, but this idea for getting there cheaper has been brewing for a few years, and while I’ve yet to sit down and do the math, it has gotten to a place where it seems intuitive enough to work.
Before I go into the solution, let’s look at the problem. At present, out best way of getting to space involves stacking explosives as high as we can, sitting on top with a countdown, and hoping that we planned for all the eventualities.</description></item><item><title>Future of Flight: Spontaneous trip to Paris</title><link>http://brysgo.com/post/2017-10-17-future-airplanes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/post/2017-10-17-future-airplanes/</guid><description>I want to go to France, I didn&amp;rsquo;t plan to go, I was just waking on the highline and was like, I think I want to go to Paris. I take out my phone, and open my air travel app and put in Paris. It tells me how much it costs, and I click accept. It takes me to a border patrol and security flow where I need to answer some lame questions, but it isn&amp;rsquo;t so bad.</description></item><item><title>Wishlist: Chromebook search/ctrl</title><link>http://brysgo.com/2015/04/29/chromebook-search-ctrl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 15:11:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/2015/04/29/chromebook-search-ctrl/</guid><description>In order to do development on my Chromebook, I need to change the search key to a control key. Problem is the search key is really sexy, and while I can make the control key the search key, it just isn&amp;rsquo;t the same. Also, sometimes I actually try and use Ctrl like a control key and everything is wonky.
So here is my request. I want to be able to set the search key to bring up the search if I haven’t pressed any keys in combination with it, but if I have, it should act like a control key.</description></item><item><title>Wishlist: Google Calendar Trips</title><link>http://brysgo.com/2014/12/23/wishlist-google-calendar-trips/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 15:24:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/2014/12/23/wishlist-google-calendar-trips/</guid><description>Google calendar has many features I rely on, one of my favorites is the integration with Google now that helps you get where you need to go on time.
I use the to make sure I always leave time for the subway. However, sometimes my trips are a little longer. Google already knows when I&amp;rsquo;m going on a flight, why not add trips to my calendar.
If I&amp;rsquo;m going on a train to long island two hours of my time are spent on the train.</description></item><item><title>Wishlist: Coding in the Cloud (without falling from the sky)</title><link>http://brysgo.com/2014/07/28/wishlist-coding-in-the-cloud-without-falling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 09:01:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/2014/07/28/wishlist-coding-in-the-cloud-without-falling/</guid><description>As a diehard Google fanboy, it is my duty to figure out how I can switch to a Chromebook as my primary laptop. The only way I can see myself doing that is if I were provided a web based programming experience that was better than coding on metal.
Enter Bryan&amp;rsquo;s fantasy world, where a flourishing space economy affords us with cheap vacations to the moon and once a year visits to grandma on the mars colony.</description></item><item><title>Wishlist Series</title><link>http://brysgo.com/2014/07/27/wishlist-series/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 21:55:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/2014/07/27/wishlist-series/</guid><description>Those of you who know me already know I am a man of many wishes and dreams. That means as a developer, I dream up, try to start, and abandon many&amp;hellip;many projects.
When I work occasionally to get these projects out of my head and into code, I will pull on any open source threads I am given. The really cool part about this is I usually end up finding the people who are already trying to do what I am setting out to do.</description></item></channel></rss>