<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pandemic on BRYSGO</title><link>http://brysgo.com/tags/pandemic/</link><description>Recent content in pandemic on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 23:36:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://brysgo.com/tags/pandemic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quarantine Rule #2: Play Video Games</title><link>http://brysgo.com/post/2020-04-09-video-games/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/post/2020-04-09-video-games/</guid><description>While we are physically isolated from each-other, we are missing the ability to go out and make new experiences with the people we care about as well as spontaneous experiences with people we&amp;rsquo;ve never seen before.
We are all connected with each-other via the internet, but the internet lacks the richness of experiences that you get in the real world. While this is true to some degree, if you dive into the world of video games, you will quickly realize that it can provide some pretty incredible experiences that make you forget you are at home in your apartment.</description></item><item><title>Quarantine Rule #1: Exercise every day</title><link>http://brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-workout/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-workout/</guid><description>It may sound like a lot, but if you are like me and your quarantine space is limited to a studio apartment, then it is probably the most essential thing you can do to stay sane. The three groups of exercise I alternate between are:
Anaerobic Aerobic Stretching As an experienced introvert, it may not come as a surprise to you that exercise is one of the things I tend to go long periods neglecting, but in this new COVID-19 world, I decided it was mission critical so I went on a YouTube research quest to figure out what I was going to do for exercise.</description></item><item><title>Quarantine Tips from Experienced Introvert</title><link>http://brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-life/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://brysgo.com/post/2020-04-05-quarantine-life/</guid><description>The year is 2003. It is a lovely spring day and I can see out my window where the trees and birds sing. Then a yell comes from downstairs, it is my mother telling me it is so nice out I should come outside. The temptation is strong, but the draw of my new computer that I had been obsessing over is even stronger.
Fast-forward to 2020. COVID-19 terrorizes the world and we are all forced to quarantine until god knows when.</description></item></channel></rss>