<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>quarantine on BRYSGO</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/tags/quarantine/</link><description>Recent content in quarantine on BRYSGO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 08:04:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.brysgo.com/tags/quarantine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GitHub Inbox Zero</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-14-GitHub-Inbox-Zero-9892d6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 08:04:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-14-GitHub-Inbox-Zero-9892d6/</guid><description>I recently reached inbox zero on GitHub for the first time in a long time. A while ago I got freaked out by the possibility of people stealing my secret keys through CI and I disabled my CI tokens on my zillion GitHub repos. It was all broken windows from there. Before I knew it my GitHub was a graveyard of packages with out of date dependencies that I had no time to update.</description></item><item><title>Dumpling Pancakes</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-11-Dumpling-Pancakes-07c1af/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 08:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-08-11-Dumpling-Pancakes-07c1af/</guid><description>I think it is safe to say that a lot of people like dumplings 🥟- and more safe to say that they are too complicated and time consuming for most people to make themselves (yes, you could order them but that is besides the point). I realized I could make dumplings by dipping the protein in a thick batter instead of wrapping it.
The benefit was this was a little bit easier, however, it still required an action per small food piece.</description></item><item><title>Seitan is a dish best served cold</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 08:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-19-Seitan-is-a-dish-bes-3e4706/</guid><description>My first kitchen obsession of the quarantine season, was Seitan. The reason being that it is delicious, and I can make it entirely with ingredients shipped via Amazon. While this mostly appeals to me because I didn&amp;rsquo;t much feel like going to the super market, it also helped that I&amp;rsquo;m a huge nerd and I like the idea of creating something out of simple powdered ingredients.
It was a bumpy road to getting it right.</description></item><item><title>Kitchen Experiments: the weirdest way to cook</title><link>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.brysgo.com/post/2020-07-15-Kitchen-Experiments-274184/</guid><description>As COVID-19 settled in and the outside food procurement grew fraught with uncertainty, I turned to something I managed to avoid for a very long time&amp;hellip; cooking.
My solution to this problem was to geek out on my love of science, minimalism, and efficiency to create tasty, weird, nutritious food that doesn&amp;rsquo;t upset my stomach or other parts of my body. You may be wondering about that last one, but I can assure you, when you start playing with discrete chemical ingredients to make your food, having the wrong combination of foods can lead to a unique experience.</description></item></channel></rss>